请看听力部分第一节。
part of part.
第一节，听下面五段对话，
每段对话后有一个小题。
after each conversation.
从题中所给的
A, B, C next seconds read the of first
三个选项。
公，选出最佳选项。
听完每段对话后，你都有十秒钟的时间来回答有关小题和阅读下一小题。
每段对话仅读一遍。
现在你有。
有五秒钟的时间阅读第一小题的有关内容。
Now, think you should try hard to get that job.
You should do careful research to prepare for the interview.
Thanks, but I've changed my mind.
Why should I go to those job interviews?
I'd like to be my own boss.
Excuse me. I'm sorry that these books were due yesterday.
That's okay. You know, you need to pay a fine for that, right?
That's one dollar and fifty cents total.
Hello. Can I help you with anything?
Yes. I'm here to see the flat.
I saw your ad about a room for rent.
Oh, you've come to the wrong door.
The flat for rent is one floor up.
Does your grandma still live in your hometown?
Yes. She says she can take care of herself, though her hearing is going.
She'd love to have her children go back and stay with her, but she wouldn't come to
live with us.
That's typical of people of her age.
Thank three A, B, and
第一节到此结束。
第二节，听下面五段对话或独白。
每段对话或独白后有几个小题。
从题中所给的
三个选项中选出最佳选项。
听每段对话或独白前，你将有时间
to After Come on.
阅读各个小题，每小题
五秒钟。
听完后，各小题将给出五秒钟的作答时间。
每段对话或独白读两遍。
听下面一段对话，回答第六和第七两个。
小题。
现在你有十秒钟的时间
阅读这两个小题。
It's time to go.
We promised Mum not to be late.
Just hold your horses.
What's the hurry anyway?
Well, I've got to stop and put gas in the car first.
That won't take long.
Well, it won't if there is no line there.
But I'm not quite ready.
I'll give you more minutes.
Then I'm going on without you.
You wouldn't do that to me.
Oh yes, I would.
on. It's time to go.
We promised Mum not to be late.
Just hold your horses.
What's the hurry anyway?
Well, I've got to stop and put gas in the car first.
That won't take long.
Well, it won't if there is no line there.
But I'm not quite ready.
I'll give you five more minutes.
Then I'm going on without you.
You wouldn't do that to me.
Oh yes, I would.
听下面一段对话，回答第八和第九两个小题。
现在你有十秒钟的时间
阅读这两。
小题。
Hello, Sophia. Simon, I owe you an apology.
I shouldn't have said nothing and left the party suddenly.
You know, I was in such a hurry that I nearly knocked over the table with glasses of
wine. Oh, forget it.
You I such wine.
Joshua told me your dad had an accident.
How is he now?
Much better. He hurt his knee in his office and he's now at home.
He will have his last appointment with the doctor next Monday.
I guess he'll be able to get back to work soon.
Hello, Sophia. Simon, I owe you an apology.
I shouldn't have said nothing and left the party suddenly.
You know, I was in such a hurry that I nearly knocked over the table with glasses of
wine. Oh, forget it.
Joshua told me your dad had an accident.
How is he now?
Much better. He hurt his knee in his office and he's now at home.
He will have his last appointment with the doctor next Monday.
I guess he'll be able to get back to work soon.
听下面一段对话。
回答第十至第十二三个小题。
现在你有十五秒钟的时间
阅读这三个小题。
Hey, Jim. How are you?
Hi, Tracy. Why are you carrying so many books?
Do you need any help?
No, thanks. I'm going to the library to return them.
It's not far away.
I've just finished my term paper for my world history class.
How are you doing?
Very busy, though.
I just got off work.
I'm about to get something to eat.
I hear you've changed your job.
Where are you working now?
ABC Company, as a computer programmer.
It's a good job, but a bit difficult for me now.
It requires a lot of work.
Well, I'm sure you can manage.
Now, I'd better let you go get some food.
Yeah, it's great seeing you again.
Hey, Jim. How are you?
Hi, Tracy. Why are you carrying so many books?
Do you need any help?
No, thanks. I'm going to the library to return them.
It's not far away.
I've just finished my term paper for my world history class.
How are you doing?
I'm going to get something to eat.
I hear you've changed your job.
Where are you working now?
ABC Company, as a computer programmer.
It's a good job, but a bit difficult for me now.
It requires a of work.
Well, I'm sure you can manage.
Now, I'd better let you go get some food.
Yeah, it's great seeing you again.
听下面一段对话，回答第十三至第十六
四个小题。
现在你有二十秒钟的时间。
阅读这四个小题。
Good is Meeting Artists.
Good This Artists.
Artists. Good Artists.
Good evening. This is Meeting Artists.
Our guest today is James Patrick Kuhn, the HAPI artist.
Mr. Kuhn is famous for his colorful murals, that is, pictures painted on a wall.
Welcome, HAPI. Our audience is curious about how you got your name.
My initials are JP.
In Spanish, they are pronounced half pay, and my Mexican friends called me so when
we were in Mexico.
What inspired you to become an artist?
My father was an oil painting artist.
He used to work in the living room.
One day when I was six, I put some paint on one of his paintings when he was out.
First he was mad.
Then he laughed.
That was all it took to make me an artist.
How do you describe your work?
My work speaks to the five -year -olds in all of us.
Though we become experienced when we grow up, we are always five years old at heart.
We all want to have fun.
That's unique idea, which is why your art is so special.
Thank you very much for coming, HAPI, and for bringing us so much happiness.
Good evening. This is Meeting Artists.
Our guest today is James Patrick Kuhn, the HAPI artist.
Mr. Kuhn is famous for his colorful murals, that is, pictures painted on a wall.
Welcome, HAPI. Our audience is curious about how you got your name.
My initials are JP.
In Spanish, they are pronounced half pay, and my Mexican friends called me so when
we were in Mexico.
What inspired you to become an artist?
My father was an oil painting artist.
He used to work in the living room.
One day when I was six, I put some paint on one of his paintings when he was out.
First he was mad.
Then he laughed.
That was all it took to make me an artist.
How do you describe your work?
My work speaks to the five -year -olds in all of us.
Though we become experienced when we grow up, we are always five years old at heart.
We all want to have fun.
That's unique idea, which is why your art is so special.
Thank you very much for coming, HAPI, and for bringing us so much happiness.
听下面一段独白，回答第十七至第二十四个小题。
现在你有二十秒。
小钟的时间阅读这四个小题。
Thank you very much HAPI.
Good morning. Welcome to the Language Center of our university.
We aim at helping people improve their language ability in several languages.
Now, I'll focus on one of our programs, the English Training Program, which I think
you might be interested in.
The program offers year -round English courses in eight levels, from beginning to
advanced. It offers a wide variety of courses for students, scholars, and
professionals. Participants can prepare for study at an American university, improve
their language skills and knowledge of U.S.
culture needed for their jobs.
The strength of the program is its ability to offer courses that are specially
designed to meet any student's specific needs and goals.
Most students in this program study full -time, which consists of 20 hours a week.
On the first day of the program, you take a test to determine your level.
At the end of each seven -week session, your language skills are evaluated, and if
you have made enough progress, you are promoted to the next level.
In addition, you can enter the Language Center bonus project, which will allow you
to have extra English hours with a native speaker.
For more practice chances, there are also several social activities and field trips
organized by the Student Center.
Good morning. Welcome to the Language Center of our university.
We aim at helping people improve their language ability in several languages.
Now, I'll focus on one of our programs,
the English Training Program, which I think you might be interested in.
The program offers year -round English courses in eight levels, from beginning to
advanced. It offers a wide variety of courses for students, scholars, and
professionals. Participants can prepare for study at an American university, improve
their language skills and knowledge of U.S.
culture needed for their jobs.
The strength of the program is its ability to offer courses that are specially
designed to meet any student's specific needs and goals.
Most students in this program study full -time, which consists of 20 hours a week.
On the first day of the program, you take a test to determine your level.
At the end of each seven -week session, your language skills are evaluated, and if
you have made enough progress, you are promoted to the next level.
In addition, you can enter the Language Center bonus project, which will allow you
to have extra English hours with a native speaker.
For more practice chances, there are also several social activities and field trips
organized by the Student Center.
第二节到此结束。
现在你有两分钟的时间，将试卷上的答案
转涂到答题卡上。
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. you.
you. you. Thank you.
Thank Thank
听力部分第一次考试到此结束。